♪Secretly keying love into the program♪
♪แอบเขียนความรักเข้าไปในโปรแกรม♪
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Thinking of you is written all over the binary♪
♪เขียนว่าคิดถึงคุณในเลขฐานสองจนเต็ม♪
♪Save and back up every word of concern♪
♪แบ็กอัปทุกความห่วงใยของคุณ♪
♪Two hearts growing closer♪
♪หัวใจสองดวงค่อย ๆ ใกล้ชิด♪
♪Every tap, every key♪
♪ทุกครั้งที่คลิก♪
♪The codes are saying I like you♪
♪โค้ดก็คือชอบคุณ♪
♪I'll brave through the night♪
♪ฉันจะผ่านค่ำคืนมืดมิด♪
♪For us, I'll work hard to defeat the BUG♪
♪ฉันจะตั้งใจเอาชนะบั๊กเพื่อคุณ♪
♪Always on standby, never lag, never hang♪
♪สแตนบายตลอดเวลา ไม่เคยเครื่องค้าง♪
♪Just to meet you♪
♪เพียงเพื่อได้พบคุณ♪
♪Want to be together and live in your arms♪
♪อยากจะอยู่ด้วยกัน เข้าไปในหัวใจคุณ♪
♪Spend the four seasons together♪
♪ผ่านฤดูทั้งสี่ฤดู♪
♪I'll key in you and I♪
♪ป้อนข้อมูลและแก้ไข♪
♪In every special and sweet program♪
♪ทุกโปรแกรมมหัศจรรย์ และแสนหวานของฉันกับคุณ♪
=Episode 11=
=ตอนที่ 11=
(PK)
(แบทเทิล)
Brother Lei.
เหลยเกอ
Did I scare you?
ทำให้นายตกใจ
Are you all right?
ไม่เป็นไรใช่ไหม
I'm okay.
ไม่เป็นไร ๆ
My best friend.
เพื่อนที่ดีที่สุดของฉัน
You look especially beautiful today.
วันนี้เธอดูสวยสุด ๆ ไปเลย
You're acting unaccountably nice.
ทำดีหวังผล
Can we have a word?
ขอคุยด้วยหน่อย
I...
ฉันนะ
I only want to know
ฉันอยากรู้ว่าเสี่ยวชีเพื่อนสนิทเธอ
if Xiaoqi has a boyfriend.
เขามีแฟนหรือเปล่า
What are you planning?
นายคิดจะทำอะไร
I think
ฉันก็คิดว่า
a pretty and cute girl like her
ผู้หญิงที่สวยน่ารักขนาดนั้น
needs to be protected.
จะต้องมีคนรักคอยดูแล
Can you send me her contact?
ช่วยส่งวีแชตเขาให้ฉันหน่อยได้ไหม
I need to get her permission first.
งั้นฉันต้องถามก่อนว่าเขาโอเคไหม
Of course.
ต้องถาม
Of course, you have to.
ใช่ต้องถาม
Ask her now.
เธอถามตอนนี้เลย
Now.
ถามตอนนี้เลย
I'll wait for you.
ฉันจะรอ
I've sent it to you.
ส่งให้นายแล้ว
It only took her an instant to reply.
ตอบไวขนาดนี้เลย
I'll buy you a meal.
ครั้งหน้าเลี้ยงข้าวเธอนะ
Da Huang.
ต้าหวง
Didn't Mr. Jiang tell us
ประธานเจียงเคยบอกแล้วนี่
to keep a distance from colleagues of opposite genders?
พนักงานชายหญิงต้องรักษาระยะห่าง
Where did you put your hand?
มือนายทำอะไร
I...
ผม...
I was just...
ผมก็แค่ถามเขา
I was asking her...
แค่ถามเขา
I was sentimental.
พอดีอารมณ์ได้
Sure.
พอเลย ๆ
Get ready.
ทุกคนเตรียมตัวกันหน่อย
The investor will be right here.
นักลงทุนใกล้จะมาแล้ว
Hurry up.
เร็ว
Sure.
ครับ ๆ
Brother Lei.
เหลยเกอ
Are you ready?
เตรียมพร้อมไหม
Yes.
พร้อมแล้ว
Here.
มา
This is the demo.
นี่เดโม
Sure.
ได้ ๆ
Mr. Jiang
คิดไม่ถึงว่าประธานเจียง
is wearing a checkered shirt.
ถึงกับใส่เชิ้ตด้วย
It shows that
นั่นสิ
Mr. Jiang is determined
วันนี้ประธานเจียงรักษามาดให้ดูดี
to win EG over.
คว้าเงินลงทุนของอีจีมาให้ได้
Those who don't know will think that you're going to seduce them.
ถ้าไม่รู้คงคิดว่านายจะใช้แผนชายงามซะอีก
That's part of my plan too.
ฉันก็ว่าจะทำแบบนั้น
I'll sacrifice my body to win our investor over.
ยอมเอาตัวเขาแลกเพื่อเงินลงทุน
They are here.
มาแล้ว
The investor is a lady.
ที่แท้ก็เป็นนักลงทุนหญิง
A young and beautiful investor.
นักลงทุนหญิงที่สวยอายุน้อยขนาดนี้
Mr. Jiang is truly blessed.
ประธานเจียงโชคดีแล้ว
This is my first time seeing such a beautiful investor.
เพิ่งเคยเจอนักลงทุนที่สวยขนาดนี้ครั้งแรก
It's you?
คุณเองเหรอ
Mr. Jiang.
ประธานเจียง
I am the representative of EG Gaming,
ฉันเป็นตัวแทนนักลงทุนของบริษัทเกมอีจี
Li Man.
หลีม่าน
Senior Yiming.
รุ่นพี่อี้หมิง
It's been a while.
ไม่เจอกันนานเลยนะคะ
That's too flattering.
ไม่กล้าหรอกครับ
Miss Li is a distinguished guest.
คุณหลีเป็นแขก
You shall just address me by my position title.
เรียกตำแหน่งผมจะเหมาะกว่า
I've long heard about
ฉันได้ยินมานานแล้วว่าบริษัทนี้
your company's rising reputation in the domestic industry.
เป็นบริษัทใหม่ชั้นแนวหน้าของประเทศ
I'm here to observe and learn
ดังนั้นครั้งนี้จึงตั้งใจมาศึกษาเรียนรู้
from the products of Mr. Jiang's company.
ผลิตภัณฑ์บริษัทประธานเจียงสักหน่อย
Hopefully,
หวังว่าพวกเราจะมีโอกาส
we'll get to work together.
ได้ร่วมงานกันนะคะ
I don't want to waste your time.
คงไม่รบกวนเวลาคุณหลีหรอกครับ
We won't work with you.
พวกเราขอปฏิเสธความร่วมมือ
Mr. Jiang.
ประธานเจียง
What do you mean?
คุณหมายความว่าไงครับ
Yicheng.
อี้เฉิง
Can we talk in private?
พวกเราคุยกันส่วนตัวหน่อยได้ไหมคะ
Sure.
ได้
We'll talk here.
ตรงนี้แหละ
Please
ทั้งสองท่าน
come with me.
เชิญตามผมมาครับ
Let's give them some privacy.
ทุกคนหลบไปก่อน
Sure.
ครับ
The bosses are having a talk.
บอสคุยงาน
We shall give them some privacy.
ทุกคนหลบไปก่อน
He told you to leave.
ให้เธอหลบ
What are you looking at?
จะมามองอะไร
What's wrong with Mr. Jiang today?
วันนี้ประธานเจียงกินยาผิดหรือเปล่า
We spent so much time preparing this.
พวกเราเตรียมมาตั้งนาน
How could he reject the collaboration so easily?
ทำไมจู่ ๆ ถึงปฏิเสธล่ะ
If you want to talk about collaboration,
ถ้าคุณอยากพูดเรื่องร่วมงานกัน
I only have one thing to say.
ผมมีแค่สองคำ
I decline it.
ปฏิเสธ
It's been three years since we last saw each other.
เราไม่เจอกันสามปี
You're still as decisive as before.
คุณยังเด็ดขาดขนาดนี้
You haven't changed at all.
ไม่เปลี่ยนเลยสักนิด
I'm definitely not as fickle as Miss Li.
แน่นอนคงเปลี่ยนไปไม่เท่าคุณหลีหรอก
Did you decline the collaboration because of me?
ดังนั้นคุณปฏิเสธที่จะร่วมงานเพราะฉันเหรอ
What else can it be?
ไม่งั้นล่ะ
You don't want to collaborate with me
คุณไม่ทำงานกับฉัน
because you can't see me
เพราะคุณไม่สามารถ
purely as a business partner.
ทำเหมือนฉันเป็นเพียงเพื่อนร่วมงานได้
Am I right?
ใช่ไหมคะ
You've overcomplicated it.
คุณคิดมากไปแล้ว
I simply don't want to work with a dishonest person.
ผมแค่ไม่อยากร่วมงานกับคนที่ไม่มีคุณธรรม
Yicheng.
อี้เฉิง
How can I get you to forgive me?
ฉันต้องทำยังไงคุณถึงอภัยให้ฉัน
If Miss Li wants to catch up with me,
ถ้าคุณหลีอยากรื้อฟื้นความหลัง
I have nothing to say to you.
ผมก็ไม่มีอะไรจะพูด
You're afraid of working with me
คุณไม่กล้าเผชิญหน้ากับฉัน
because you haven't got over me.
เพราะว่าคุณยังลืมฉันไม่ได้ใช่ไหม
You've overestimated yourself.
คุณมั่นใจในตัวเองเกินไปแล้ว
Do you need me to remind you
เรื่องเมื่อสามปีก่อน
of what happened three years ago?
ต้องให้ผมเตือนความจำคุณไหม
Then, why did you refuse
แล้วก่อนหน้านี้บริษัทคุณ
to recruit female programmers before this?
ทำไมไม่เคยรับโปรแกรมเมอร์ผู้หญิงเลย
Yicheng.
อี้เฉิง
I came back for you.
ครั้งนี้ฉันกลับมาเพราะคุณนะ
Can we start all over again?
พวกเราจะเริ่มกันใหม่ได้ไหม
We can't.
ไม่ได้
Haven't you been staying single
แต่คุณก็โสดมาตลอด
because of me?
ไม่ใช่ว่ากำลังรอฉันอยู่เหรอ
Because of you?
รอคุณเหรอ
Did you see the female programmer in our office?
คุณเห็นโปรแกรมเมอร์ผู้หญิงคนนั้นไหม
Lu Li.
ลู่หลี
(Programming Department)
(แผนกโปรแกรม)
♪Secretly keying love into the program♪
♪แอบเขียนความรักเข้าไปในโปรแกรม♪
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Thinking of you is written all over the binary♪
♪เขียนว่าคิดถึงคุณในเลขฐานสองจนเต็ม♪
♪Save and back up every word of concern♪
♪แบ็กอัปทุกความห่วงใยของคุณ♪
♪Two hearts growing closer♪
♪หัวใจสองดวงค่อย ๆ ใกล้ชิด♪
♪Every tap, every key The codes are saying I like you♪
♪ทุกครั้งที่คลิกโค้ดก็คือชอบคุณ♪
♪I'll brave through the night♪
♪ฉันจะผ่านค่ำคืนมืดมิด♪
♪For us, I'll work hard♪
♪ฉันจะตั้งใจเอาชนะ♪
♪to defeat the BUG♪
♪บั๊กเพื่อคุณ♪
♪Always on standby, never lag, never hang♪
♪สแตนบายตลอดเวลา ไม่เคยเครื่องค้าง♪
♪Just to meet you♪
♪เพียงเพื่อได้พบคุณ♪
♪Want to be together♪
♪อยากจะอยู่ด้วยกัน♪
♪And live in your arms♪
♪เข้าไปในหัวใจคุณ♪
♪Spend the four seasons together♪
♪ผ่านฤดูทั้งสี่ฤดู♪
Lu.
เสี่ยวลู่ลู่
What's going on between you and Mr. Jiang?
เธอกับประธานเจียงนี่ยังไง
Tell us.
ว่ามา
How did you win Mr. Jiang's heart?
เธอไปหลอกประธานเจียงมาได้ยังไง
When did you start dating each other?
พวกเธอคบกันตอนไหน
Why haven't I noticed anything?
ทำไมฉันไม่สังเกตเห็นเลย
Who took the initiative?
เขาจีบเธอ หรือว่าเธอจีบเขา
We...
พวกเรา...
Our parents matched us up.
เราสองคนพ่อแม่จับคู่ให้
Now I know why
ไม่น่าล่ะ
you're the only exception in our department.
เป็นเคสพิเศษเฉพาะแผนกเรา
You've even met each other's parents.
ที่แท้นี่ถึงขั้นไปเจอพ่อแม่แล้ว
You are so good at keeping secrets.
พวกเธอนี่เก็บความลับใช้ได้เลยนะ
You're too lucky.
นายนี่โชคดีมากเลยนะ
Our boss' future wife interceded with the boss
ที่แท้คนที่ออกหน้าให้นายก็คือว่าที่
on your behalf.
เถ้าแก่เนี้ยเลยนะ
Exactly.
ก็นั่นนะสิ
Now I understand why.
ไม่น่า
Lu.
เสี่ยวลู่ลู่
When are you going to get married?
เธอกับประธานเจียงจะแต่งงานกันตอนไหน
This...
คือว่า...
We're not in a hurry.
เรื่องนี้ไม่รีบ
Not in a hurry?
ไม่รีบเหรอ
If you don't act fast,
เธอยังช้าอีก
someone else will snatch Mr. Jiang away from you.
ประธานเจียงคงถูกแย่งไปแล้ว
He's right.
ก็นั่นสิ
Mr. Jiang
ประธานเจียงนะ
shares a special relationship with Miss Investor.
กับนักลงทุนหญิงนั่น ความสัมพันธ์ไม่ธรรมดานะ
Precisely.
ใช่
Am I right?
ใช่ไหม
Do you know who Miss Li is?
พวกนายรู้เรื่องคุณหลีไหม
Miss Li?
คุณหลีเหรอ
Let's look it up.
หาก่อน
Let me look it up.
ฉันหาก่อนนะ
Li Man.
หลีม่าน
Twenty-seven years old.
อายุ 27
Graduated from the Faculty of Computer Science at the University of Xinhai.
จบจากสาขาคอมพิวเตอร์ มหาวิทยาลัยซินไห่
She went abroad to further her studies three years ago.
สามปีก่อนไปเรียนต่อต่างประเทศ
She's now the senior manager
ตอนนี้รับตำแหน่ง ผู้จัดการระดับสูงอยู่แผนกลงทุน
of the EG Gaming Investment Department.
บริษัทเกมอีจี
This is all the information we could acquire legally.
ข้อมูลถูกกฎหมายที่หามีแค่นี้
It's obvious now.
เรื่องชัดเจนแล้ว
That's why she called Mr. Chen senior.
ไม่น่าล่ะถึงเรียกผอ.เฉินว่ารุ่นพี่
She probably met Mr. Jiang
ที่แท้ก็รู้จักกับประธานเจียง
during their college days.
ตั้งแต่สมัยมหาวิทยาลัยแล้ว
She's likely Mr. Jiang's ex-girlfriend.
อาจจะเป็นแฟนเก่าของประธานเจียง
Has Mr. Jiang told you
ประธานเจียงเคยบอกเธอ
anything about his ex-girlfriend?
เรื่องของเขากับแฟนเก่าไหม
Yes.
จริงด้วย
Ex...
คือว่าคนก่อน...
Where did Brother Lei go?
เหลยเกอล่ะ
Lei...
เหลย...
He probably went to the washroom.
เหลยเกอไปห้องน้ำมั้ง
I'm sure he has a weak bladder.
เจ้านี่ต้องไตอ่อนแอแน่
That will make him bald too.
ไตอ่อนแอจะผมร่วงได้ง่าย
You know what.
ฉันบอกพวกนายให้นะ
You never care about balding.
พวกนายจะละเลย ปัญหาผมร่วงไม่ได้เด็ดขาด
Brother Lei.
เหลยเกอ
You need to take care of this.
ต้องให้ความสำคัญ
Old... Old Ape.
เหล่า เหล่าหยวน
For this, we need to start young.
เรื่องนี้ต้องให้ความสำคัญตั้งแต่เด็ก
Da Huang.
ต้าหวง
He's so handsome.
หล่อมากเลย
This is a nice angle.
มุมนี้หล่อมากเลย
That's true.
จริงด้วย ๆ
He looks so manly.
แมนมากเลย
Oh, my God.
พระเจ้าช่วย
He's so sexy.
เซ็กซี่มากเลย
What are you looking at?
ดูอะไรเหรอ
Mr. Jiang's photo exposing his relationship.
ภาพเปิดตัวของประธานเจียงนะ
I didn't expect him to go this far.
คิดไม่ถึงว่าจะเปิดเผยขนาดนี้
Precisely.
จริงด้วย
Let me take a look.
ขอฉันดูหน่อย
Miss Jiang.
รองผอ.เจียง
We didn't take this photo.
ภาพนี้พวกเราไม่ได้ถ่ายนะคะ
It was circulated in the chatroom.
อันนี้ส่งต่อกันมาในกลุ่ม
This...
นี่
Any more photos?
ยังมีอีกไหม
Send them to me.
ส่งให้ฉันที
My mom will be elated when she sees this.
แม่ฉันเห็นคงดีใจแย่
This is the only photo.
มีแค่ใบเดียวค่ะ
This...
นี่
Why was she there?
ทำไมเขามาอยู่นี่ได้
When was this photo taken?
ภาพนี้ถ่ายตอนไหนเหรอ
I think it was taken just now.
เหมือนว่าเพิ่งถ่ายค่ะ
Just now...
เมื่อกี้เหรอ
Just now?
เมื่อกี้
Hurry up.
เร็ว ๆ
Let's go.
ไปเถอะ ๆ
My...
คือว่า
Miss Jiang.
รองผอ.เจียงคะ
My phone.
มือถือ
Li Man.
หลีม่าน
Wait for me in the car.
พวกคุณไปรอฉันบนรถก่อน
Zitong.
จื่อถง
I'm sorry.
ขอโทษด้วยนะ
I didn't have the time to drop by and say hello.
เมื่อกี้ไม่ทันได้ไปทักทายเธอ
It doesn't matter.
ไม่เป็นไร
We're not on speaking terms anyway.
ยังไงซะเราก็ไม่ต้องทักทายกันแล้ว
I'm only here
ที่ฉันเรียกเธอ
to warn you
ก็เพราะอยากเตือนเธอ
not to disturb my brother anymore.
อย่ามาวอแวพี่ฉันอีก
It doesn't matter what happened to Yicheng and me.
ไม่ว่าฉันกับอี้เฉิงจะยังไง
Can't we stay friends?
เราสองคนจะเป็นเพื่อนกันไม่ได้แล้วเหรอ
The day you betrayed my brother
ตั้งแต่เธอวันนั้นที่เธอทรยศพี่ฉัน
and left him without a word
แล้วหายไปโดยไม่บอกลาสักคำ
was the day our friendship ended.
ฉันก็ตัดขาดกับเธอแล้ว
You probably won't believe what I'm going to say.
ฉันพูดแบบนี้เธออาจจะไม่เชื่อ
But I never intended to hurt any of you.
แต่ที่จริงฉันไม่คิดจะทำร้ายพวกเธอเลย
You were my best friend.
เธอเป็นเพื่อนที่ดีที่สุดของฉัน
Yiming is the senior I trusted the most.
อี้หมิงเป็นรุ่นพี่ที่ฉันเชื่อใจที่สุด
Yicheng
ส่วนอี้เฉิง
was the person I loved the most.
เป็นคนที่ฉันรักที่สุด
Save it.
เธอพอได้แล้ว
You love yourself the most.
คนที่เธอรักที่สุดคือตัวเองต่างหาก
Be honest.
ว่ามา
What do you want to get from my brother this time?
ครั้งนี้อยากจะได้อะไรจากพี่ฉันอีก
I'm here to make it up to him.
ที่กลับมาครั้งนี้ฉันอยากชดเชยให้
But I didn't expect to see him with a new girlfriend.
แต่ฉันคิดไม่ถึงว่าเขาจะมีแฟนแล้ว
That's why
ดังนั้น
I suggest you give up.
ฉันแนะนำให้เธอรีบตัดใจซะ
My brother and Lu Li have a very good relationship.
พี่ฉันกับลู่หลีรักกันดี
But I heard that your brother went on blind dates not long ago.
แต่เมื่อไม่นานมานี้ ฉันยังได้ยินว่าพี่เธอไปดูตัว
I suppose they just got together.
พวกเขาน่าจะคบกันได้ไม่นานนะ
So what?
แล้วยังไง
Even if they have only been dating each other for around two weeks,
ต่อให้พวกเขาคบกันแค่สิบกว่าวัน
my brother will never get affected by you.
พี่ฉันก็ไม่มีทางหวั่นไหวกับเธอแน่
So, it's only two weeks.
ที่แท้ก็แค่ไม่สิบกว่าวัน
Anyway, I'm warning you
ยังไงซะฉันเตือนเธอไว้นะ
not to bother my brother anymore.
ห้ามคิดจะมีแผนอะไรกับพี่ฉันอีก
This is bad.
แย่แล้ว ๆ
Yiming.
พี่อี้หมิง
Something went wrong.
เกิดเรื่องแล้ว ๆ
Calm down.
ไม่ต้องรน
What happened?
เกิดเรื่องอะไร
I wanted to threaten Li Man.
เมื่อกี้ฉันไปเตือนหลีม่าน
But I accidentally told her
สุดท้ายไม่ทันระวัง
that Yicheng
พูดว่าพี่ฉันกับลู่หลี
only just started dating Lu Li.
เพิ่งคบกันได้ไม่นาน
I...
ฉัน...
Did I make a mistake?
ฉันพลั้งปากไปใช่ไหม
I reckon Li Man came back for your brother.
หลีม่านน่าพุ่งเป้ากลับมาหาพี่เธอ
Even if you didn't spill the beans,
ต่อให้เธอไม่พูด
she would discover the truth from someone else.
เขาก็น่าจะรู้จากที่อื่นอยู่ดี
How audacious of her
พี่ว่า
to come looking for my brother?
ทำไมเขายังมีหน้ากลับมาหาพี่ฉันอีกนะ
She used to be quite thin-skinned.
ก่อนหน้านี้ก็หน้าบางออก
A few years have passed.
คิดไม่ถึงว่าแค่ไม่กี่ปี
Not only has she grown some wrinkles,
ไม่เพียงแค่มีริ้วรอย
but her skin has also grown thicker.
หน้ายังหนาขึ้นอีกด้วย
This is between your brother and her.
นี่เป็นเรื่องของพี่เธอกับเขา
We shall leave it to your brother.
ทางที่ดีให้พี่เธอจัดการเอง
It will be better if we can stay away from this.
เธออย่าไปยุ่งจะดีกว่า
Sure.
ได้
I'll do as you say.
เอาตามพี่ว่า
Why are you staring at me?
เธอมัวจ้องฉันทำไม
Because you look good.
พี่หล่อไง
Zitong.
จื่อถง
We need to talk about work.
เราต้องมาคุยปัญหา เรื่องงานของเธอหน่อยนะ
Do you know what your department is up to?
เธอรู้ไหมว่าแผนกเธอทำอะไรอยู่
I think they are coming up with a tagline for the game.
เหมือนว่ากำลังทำคำโฆษณาเกมมั้ง
They completed it a long time ago.
นั่นสรุปไปนานแล้ว
Why are you showing concern to our department?
ทำไมพี่ถึงได้สนใจเรื่องแผนกเราขนาดนี้
I'm not showing concern to them.
ไม่ใช่ว่าฉันสนใจ
It's just that you're acting too unconcerned.
แต่เธอไม่สนใจต่างหาก
You are very blessed and privileged.
เธอเกิดมาพร้อมทุกอย่าง
You said a few words, and you got a position
แค่เอ่ยปากก็สามารถได้ตำแหน่ง
others have to work hard for years to reach.
ที่คนอื่นพยายามทำงานหลายปีแล้ว
Look at yourself.
แล้วเธอล่ะ
You're occupying a position others longing for,
อยู่ในตำแหน่งที่คนอื่นให้ความสำคัญ
and what have you done?
ทำอะไรบ้าง
But...
แต่ว่า...
They don't really need me.
พวกเขาก็ไม่มีอะไรให้ฉันต้องทำนี่
Then, why are you here?
แล้วเธอมาบริษัททำไม
I'm here to win your heart.
จีบพี่ไง
I've spent all my energy
ฉันเอาพลังทั้งหมด
on you.
ที่ฉันมีมาชอบพี่แล้วไง
Can I only be praised when I work hard?
หรือว่าคนที่ขยันทำงานควรได้รับคำชม
Is it wrong to put in my effort to get your attention?
การพยายามชอบใครสักคนมันผิดหรือไง
I'll get you another cup of coffee.
ฉันไปรินกาแฟให้เธออีกแก้วนะ
Miss Man.
พี่ม่าน
Are you all right?
คุณโอเคไหมคะ
I didn't expect today to be a good day.
ฉันเคยคิดว่าวันนี้คงไม่ราบรื่น
But I didn't expect it would be this bad too.
แต่ก็คิดไม่ถึงว่าจะจบแบบอนาถขนาดนี้
Mr. Jiang is a difficult man.
อารมณ์ของประธานเจียง ไม่ใช่คนทั่วไปจะรับมือได้
But he looks much more handsome in person.
แต่ตัวจริงหล่อกว่าในภาพเยอะเลย
He used to have a worse temper.
ก่อนหน้านี้เขานิสัยเสียกว่านี้อีก
Whenever he faced challenges during coding,
โดยเฉพาะตอนที่เขียนโปรแกรมไม่ได้ดั่งใจ
no one in the company dared utter a word.
คนทั้งบริษัทไม่มีใครกล้าพูดอะไร
But he looks way more mature now.
แต่ตอนนี้เขาดูสุขุมขึ้นเยอะแล้ว
The female staff in his company
ผู้หญิงที่บริษัทเขาคนนั้น
looks very ordinary.
ดูธรรมดามาก
She's no match for you.
ห่างกับคุณไกลเลย
She resembles my old self.
เขาเหมือนกับฉันเมื่อก่อนมาก
Didn't you say
คุณบอกว่าหลายปีนี้
that Mr. Jiang had been single for the past few years?
ประธานเจียงเป็นโสดมาตลอดไม่ใช่เหรอ
Perhaps,
ไม่แน่นะ
he found someone who resembles you
เขาแค่ดึงเอาคนที่คล้ายกับคุณ
to upset you on purpose.
จงใจยั่วโมโหคุณ
(Will she be upset because I kissed her out of the blue?)
(เขาคงไม่โกรธที่ฉันจู่ ๆ ไปจูบเขาหรอกนะ)
Li Man gave me a call.
หลีม่านโทรมาหาฉัน
She invited us for dinner.
บอกว่าจะนัดเรากินข้าว
She specifically asked you to bring along your girlfriend.
แล้วยังกำชับว่าให้นายพาแฟนไปด้วย
You can go ahead if you want.
นายจะไปก็ไปเอง
We won't be there.
พวกเราไม่ไป
She wants to see
เขาน่าจะอยากเห็นนายกับลู่หลี
if you're really dating Lu Li,
ว่าคบกันจริง
or it's just a lie.
หรือว่าเล่นละครตบตาเขา
Send me the address.
งั้นนายส่งที่อยู่ให้ฉัน
Everyone.
มา ทุกคน
Listen up.
พวกนายฟังให้ดีนะ
Make sure
ฝุ่นทุกที่
to clean every corner.
จะต้องเช็ดให้สะอาดเลยนะ
Brother Lei.
เหลยเกอ
Pay more attention
โดยเฉพาะที่ของเสี่ยวลู่
to Lu's place.
ละเอียดหน่อย
If the dust clogs your hair follicles,
ถ้าเกิดว่ารูขุมขนบนหนังศีรษะมีฝุ่นอุดตันละก็
it will cause seborrheic hair loss.
จะทำให้ผมร่วงจากผิวหนังอักเสบได้
Yes.
ใช่ ๆ
It doesn't matter if we lose our hair.
พวกเราผมร่วงไม่มีปัญหาหรอก
How can our boss' future wife suffer from hair loss?
แต่จะให้เถ้าแก่เนี้ย ในอนาคตผมร่วงได้ยังไง
Leave this to me.
เรื่องเล็กแค่นี้ให้ฉันทำเถอะ
You can take a rest.
เธอไปพักเถอะ
Lu.
เสี่ยวลู่
This job fits me just right.
งานนี้เหมาะกับฉันมาก
It helps in relieving stress.
คลายเครียด
(Work plan) I'll do it.
ฉันทำเอง
You can take a rest.
เธอกลับไปพักเถอะ
Leader Zhang.
หัวหน้าจาง
Do you need anything?
แผนกคุณนี่ขาดอุปกรณ์หรือเปล่า
Yes. We do.
ขาด ๆ
I need a new keyboard.
ผมจะเปลี่ยนคีย์บอร์ดใหม่
Didn't you get a new keyboard early this year?
คุณเพิ่งเปลี่ยนไปเมื่อต้นปีนี่
But Lu Li...
แต่ว่าลู่หลี
I think your computer is two years old.
คอมพิวเตอร์คุณเหมือนว่าจะสองปีแล้ว
I'll get you a new one later.
เดี๋ยวฉันเปลี่ยนเครื่องใหม่ให้นะ
That's not necessary.
ไม่เป็นไรค่ะ
I work well with this one.
เครื่องนี้ใช้ถนัดมือดีอยู่แล้ว
It's okay.
ไม่เป็นไร ๆ
Besides, it's so dangerous to sit in this chair.
เก้าอี้นี่นั่งอันตรายเกินไปหรือเปล่า
We have a chair similar to Mr. Jiang's in the store.
ในคลังมีแบบเดียวกับประธานเจียง
You can use it.
เอามาให้คุณใช้พอดี
Yes.
ใช่ ๆ
That's not necessary.
ไม่เป็นไรค่ะ ๆ
You don't need to give me any special treatment.
ทุกคนไม่ต้องดูแลฉันเป็นพิเศษหรอก
Mr. Jiang won't get affected
ท่าทีของพวกคุณที่มีต่อฉัน
by what you do to me.
ก็คงไม่ได้ส่งผลอะไร กับประธานเจียงหรอก
I can't change his mind.
ฉันก็ชักนำความคิดเขาไม่ได้หรอก
We shall stay the same.
พวกเราทำเหมือนเมื่อก่อนเลย
We saw
ประธานเจียงทำกับคุณยังไง
how well Mr. Jiang treated you.
วันนี้เราเห็นกันหมดแล้ว
You will definitely
อนาคตเถ้าแก่เนี้ยของบริษัท
be our boss' future wife.
จะต้องเป็นคุณแน่นอน
Yes.
ใช่ ๆ
You can't make jokes like this.
เรื่องนี้ห้ามเอามาล้อเล่นนะ
Mr. Jiang doesn't like to mention his personal affairs
ประธานเจียงไม่ชอบเอาเรื่องส่วนตัว
at work.
มาพูดในที่ทำงาน
Don't mention it again.
จากนี้อย่าพูดอีกนะคะ
There are so many of you here.
ครึกครื้นขนาดนี้เลย
Mr. Jiang.
ประธานเจียง
We're here to check the supplies.
พวกเรามาดูว่าอุปกรณ์มีปัญหาไหม
Yes.
ใช่ค่ะ
Get back to work then.
งั้นพวกคุณก็ทำงานกันเถอะ
Lu Li.
ลู่หลี
We'll have dinner together later.
คืนนี้รอไปกินข้าวกับผมนะ
He came here personally to ask you out for dinner.
นัดกินข้าวยังมาบอกด้วยตัวเองด้วย
Lu Li.
ลู่หลี
Mr. Jiang does care a lot about you.
ประธานเจียงให้ความสำคัญกับคุณจริงนะ
Precisely.
จริงด้วย ๆ
All the girls in the company
สาว ๆ ในบริษัท
will have their hearts broken.
ใจสลายกันหมดแล้ว
Exactly.
จริงด้วย
Don't forget to pass us the wedding candy
ตอนแต่งงาน
when you get married.
อย่าลืมชวนเราไปด้วยนะ
Remember to pass us the wedding candy.
อย่าลืมชวนเราไปนะ
Wedding candy.
ชวนไปด้วยนะ
Let's go.
ไปเถอะ ๆ
Lu Li.
ชวนด้วยนะ
Send us your wedding candy.
ชวนเราไปกินร่วมงานด้วยนะ
Let's go.
ไปเถอะ ๆ
Mr. Jiang is torturing all the single men in public.
ประธานเจียงนี่คือโชว์หวานอย่างเปิดเผย
No.
ไม่ ๆ
There's no need for that.
ไม่ต้องหรอก
Excuse me.
เอาขาหลบหน่อย
It's much clearer now.
เหมือนขึ้นเป็นจุดนะ
There's some dust here.
มีฝุ่น
It's dusty here.
ดูสิตรงนี้สกปรก
Xiaoqi.
เสี่ยวชี
Sorry
ขอโทษทีนะ
to have kept you waiting.
ปล่อยให้คุณรอนาน
I came early.
ฉันมาเร็วนะ
Where's Lu Li?
ลู่หลีล่ะ
She's on a date with Mr. Jiang.
ไปเดตกับประธานเจียงแล้ว
It's just the two of us now.
ตอนนี้เหลือแค่เราสองคนแล้ว
You know about her and Jiang Yicheng...
คุณรู้แล้วเหรอว่าเขากับเจียงอี้เฉิง
We just found out today.
เพิ่งรู้วันนี้
When Mr. Jiang publicly announced
ตอนที่ประธานเจียงประกาศ
that Lu Li was his girlfriend,
ต่อหน้าทุกคนว่าลู่หลีเป็นแฟนเขา
we were all astounded.
ทั้งบริษัทก็ลือกันทั่ว
What do you want to eat?
คุณอยากกินอะไร
I...
ผม
I'll buy you a meal.
ผมเลี้ยง
Xiaoqi.
เสี่ยวชี
Why are you here?
เธอมาได้ยังไง
I'm not here for you.
ยังไงซะก็ไม่ได้มาหานาย
Director Gu, you...
ผอ.กู้ คุณ...
Do you know each other?
พวกคุณรู้จักกันเหรอ
He's my brother.
เขาเป็นพี่ฉัน
Where are you going?
พวกเธอจะไปไหนกัน
We're going to grab some food.
พวกเราตั้งใจจะไปหาอะไรกิน
Do you want to join us?
ไปด้วยกันไหมครับ
Why did you invite him along?
ชวนเขาทำไม
He'll ruin my appetite.
ทำให้ไม่อยากอาหาร
All right.
ใช่ ๆ
I have no plan for dinner yet.
พอดีว่าฉันก็ไม่รู้ไปไหน
Let's go together.
ไปสิ
He... He's so bold.
คือ ไม่เกรงใจเลยเหรอ
Director Gu seems quite distant in the office.
ปกติแล้วอยู่บริษัทผอ.กู้ดูเย็นชา
He's really caring in private.
ส่วนตัวแล้วก็ดูแลเก่งเหมือนกันนะครับ
He's a germophobe.
เขาอนามัยนะ
He's not only troublesome,
ปกติแล้วตัวเองเรื่องเยอะไม่พอ
but also controlling.
ยังยุ่งเรื่องคนอื่นด้วย
Why don't you call me controlling
ปกติเวลาตอนจัดห้องให้เธอ
when I clean up the house for you?
ไม่เห็นว่าฉันชอบยุ่งเลย
You insist on cleaning it up, okay?
นายจะเก็บทำให้ได้ต่างหาก
Here.
มาครับ
Have some meat.
กินเนื้อหน่อย
You're so thin.
คุณผอมขนาดนี้
Are you on a diet?
ปกติแล้วลดน้ำหนักเหรอ
She's on a diet.
เขาเหรอลดน้ำหนัก
Instead of eating satisfyingly,
เขาก็แค่แตกต่างจาก ที่กินโดยหาเหตุผลมาสนับสนุน
she now eats fearfully.
ไปเป็นกินอย่างหวาดระแวงแค่นั้น
Gu Mo.
กู้มั่ว
Do you have to ruin my image
ต่อหน้าเพื่อนใหม่นายจะต้อง
in front of my new friend?
ให้ร้ายฉันขนาดนี้เลยเหรอ
I'm only stating the facts.
ฉันก็แค่อธิบายตามความจริง
You should stay true to yourself.
เธอต้องกล้าที่จะแสดงตัวตนจริง ๆ ออกมา
After all, you won't be able to maintain this fake image for long.
ยังไงซะภาพลักษณ์ปลอม ๆ ก็รักษาไว้ได้ไม่นาน
This is my first time hearing so many words from Director Gu.
ครั้งแรกเลยที่ได้ยินผอ.กู้พูดเยอะขนาดนี้
Now you know how two-faced he is.
คุณรู้แล้วใช่ไหมว่าเขาจอมปลอมแค่ไหน
He
เขาเนี่ยนะ
is really pompous.
ชอบวางมาดเป็นที่สุด
He always
ปกตินะ
plays an obedient boy in front of our parents.
ต่อหน้าพ่อแม่ก็ชอบทำเป็นเด็กดี
This has been affecting me
ฉันนี่ได้รับผลกระทบแต่เล็ก
since I was a kid.
ถูกทำร้าย
I see...
ที่แท้
Acting differently in front of different people doesn't make me a hypocrite.
รู้จักปรับท่าทีกับคนที่ ต่างกันไปไม่ได้เรียกว่าจอมปลอม
This only proves my capability.
แต่เป็นความสามารถ
Thanks.
ขอบคุณ
You're really capable of annoying others.
นายนี่เก่งในการทำให้คนไม่ชอบหน้านะ
I...
ผม...
I'll go get the bill.
ผมไปคิดเงินก่อนนะ
I suppose
คิดว่า
there was a traffic jam.
น่าจะรถติด
Let's wait for a while more.
รอพวกเขาอีกเดี๋ยวแล้วกัน
They'll be here soon.
น่าจะใกล้ถึงแล้ว
Do you want any juice?
คุณอยากดื่มน้ำผลไม้อะไรไหม
I'll order it for you.
ฉันสั่งให้
It's okay.
ไม่ต้องหรอก
Yicheng.
อี้เฉิง
You're here.
มาแล้วเหรอ
Have a seat.
นั่งสิ
Sure.
ได้
Lu Li.
ลู่หลี
You can sit here.
นั่งนี่สิ
Yicheng.
อี้เฉิง
I'm very happy to have you here.
ฉันดีใจมากที่วันนี้คุณมาได้
Didn't you say you want to meet Lu Li?
คุณบอกอยากเจอลู่หลีไม่ใช่เหรอ
I brought her along.
ผมพาเขามาแล้ว
Miss Lu.
คุณลู่
Please excuse us.
อย่าถือสาเลยนะคะ
It's been a few years since Yicheng, Yiming, and I
ฉันกับอี้เฉิงแล้วก็รุ่นพี่อี้หมิง
last met each other.
ไม่ได้เจอกันหลายปีแล้ว
I just found out
วันนี้เพิ่งรู้ว่า
that Yicheng has gotten himself a girlfriend.
อี้เฉิงมีแฟนแล้ว
Therefore, I really wanted to meet you.
ดังนั้นเลยอยากจะรู้จักคุณสักหน่อย
In the meantime, I can catch up with my old friends too.
ถือโอกาสให้ทุกคนจะมาเจอกันด้วย
Miss Li.
คุณหลี
I'm too flattered.
เกรงใจไปแล้วค่ะ
You've just returned home from abroad.
คุณเพิ่งกลับมา
We should be the ones hosting you.
พวกเราควรต้อนรับคุณมากกว่า
The food is getting cold.
อาหารเย็นหมดแล้ว
We'll talk as we eat.
กินไปคุยไปเถอะ
Yes.
ใช่ ๆ
Let's eat.
พวกเรากินกันเถอะ
Don't be shy.
ไม่ต้องเกรงใจนะ
The soup is nice.
น้ำแกงอร่อยนะ
I ordered it just for you.
ตั้งใจสั่งให้นายเลย
Let me stick the patch for you.
ฉันช่วยแปะให้คุณนะ
All done.
เสร็จแล้ว
You have always had neck pain.
ก่อนหน้านี้คุณก็มีปัญหาต้นคอ
Did you fail to take good care of your neck during the past few years?
หลายปีมานี้ก็ไม่ค่อยได้ดูแลใช่ไหม
I bought
ฉันเอาเครื่องนวดที่
a really nice neck massager there.
ใช้ดีมากมาจากต่างประเทศ
I'll pass it to you.
วันหลังฉันเอาให้นะ
It's okay.
ไม่เป็นไร
Lu Li can give me a massage.
มีลู่หลีช่วยนวดให้ผมก็พอ
I know how much you like seafood.
ฉันรู้ว่าคุณชอบกินของทะเล
That's why I picked this restaurant.
ก็เลยตั้งใจเลือกร้านนี้
The shrimps arrived by air today.
กุ้งที่นี่เพิ่งเข้ามาสด ๆ วันนี้เลย
Give it a taste.
ลองชิมดูสิคะ
You should try it too.
พวกคุณก็กินด้วยสิ
The shrimps are quite fresh.
กุ้งที่นี่สดมาก
Give it a taste.
รีบชิมเร็ว
Lu Li.
ลู่หลี
Aren't you allergic to seafood?
คุณแพ้อาหารทะเลไม่ใช่เหรอ
Are you allergic to seafood?
คุณแพ้อาหารทะเลเหรอ
I was.
นั่นเมื่อก่อน
I'm all good now.
ตอนนี้หายแล้ว
Do you remember when we first started our business?
ยังจำได้ว่าตอนเราเพิ่งเปิดบริษัทกันใหม่ ๆ
We went to the seaside for a team-building activity.
มีครั้งหนึ่งไปเที่ยวที่ทะเลกัน
We planned to catch some seafood and grill it.
เดิมทีคุยกันว่าจะไปจับของทะเลมาย่างกิน
We didn't manage to catch any fish,
สุดท้ายจับปลาไม่ได้
but Yicheng's hand was hurt by the crab.
มือของอี้เฉิงกลับถูกปูหนีบจนบาดเจ็บ
I cried all the way to the hospital.
ฉันตกใจร้องไห้ไปจนถึงโรงพยาบาล
Is the scar
แผลที่มือคุณตอนนี้
still there?
ยังอยู่ไหม
That was a long time ago.
ผ่านไปนานแล้ว
The scar is long gone.
แผลหายไปนานแล้ว
Eat up.
รีบกินเถอะ
I need to use the bathroom.
ฉันไปห้องน้ำหน่อย
You stay here.
พวกคุณกินกันก่อนนะ
I'll go to the bathroom too.
ผมไปเหมือนกัน
I knew you'd come after me.
ฉันรู้ว่าคุณต้องมาหาฉัน
Are you done recalling the past?
เล่นละครรำลึกความหลังพอหรือยัง
If you want to cause a rift between Lu Li and me
ถ้าคุณอยากให้ลู่หลีรู้สึกอึดอัดใจกับผม
and separate us,
และเลิกกับผมละก็
you'll be disappointed.
คุณคงผิดหวัง
Even if you refuse to forgive me,
ต่อให้คุณไม่อภัยให้ฉัน
you don't have to put up a show.
คุณก็ไม่เห็นต้องเล่นละครหลอกฉันเลย
I know that you haven't known each other for long.
ฉันรู้ว่าพวกคุณรู้จักกันได้ไม่นาน
You don't know her at all.
คุณไม่รู้จักเขาด้วยซ้ำ
Does it matter how long we've known each other?
รู้จักใครสักคนเกี่ยวกับระยะเวลาด้วยเหรอ
We've known each other for a long time.
ผมรู้จักคุณตั้งนาน
But do I really know you?
ผมรู้จักคุณจริง ๆ เหรอ
Do you really like her?
แล้วคุณชอบเขาจริง ๆ เหรอ
If you have feelings for her,
ถ้าคุณชอบลู่หลีจริง ๆ
why didn't you know about her seafood allergies?
ทำไมแม้แต่เรื่องที่เขา แพ้อาหารทะเลคุณก็ไม่รู้
I can get to know her better in the future.
ในอนาคตผมมีเวลา อีกมากที่จะค่อย ๆ รู้จักเขา
She's just a girl.
เขาเป็นแค่เด็กผู้หญิง
What can she give you?
เขาให้อะไรคุณได้
Can she help you build your career?
เรื่องงานเขาช่วยคุณได้ไหม
Yicheng.
อี้เฉิง
She's not the one for you.
เขาไม่เหมาะกับคุณจริง ๆ
Then, who's the one?
แล้วใครเหมาะกับผม
The person who betrayed our company,
คุณคนที่ทรยศบริษัท
her boyfriend,
ทรยศแฟน
and ran away with the fund?
แล้วหอบเงินหนีไปเหรอ
I'm here to tell you
วันนี้ที่ผมมาเพราะอยากบอกคุณ
that it's over.
พวกเราเป็นอดีตไปแล้ว
I won't have anything to do with you in the future.
อนาคตของผมไม่เกี่ยวอะไรกับคุณ
I need to use the bathroom too.
ฉันก็ไปห้องน้ำเหมือนกัน
That's not true.
ฉันไม่เชื่อหรอก
I'm sure you still have feelings for me.
ฉันไม่เชื่อว่าคุณไม่รู้สึกอะไรกับฉันเลย
Please behave yourself.
ระวังท่าทีด้วย
How's the allergic reaction?
คุณแพ้หนักไหม
You knew about your allergies.
ทั้งที่รู้ว่าแพ้
Yet you ate the shrimps.
คุณยังจะกิน
I've never seen someone as foolish as you.
ไม่เคยเจอคนบื้อแบบคุณมาก่อนเลย
Jiang Yicheng has feelings for Miss Li, right?
เจียงอี้เฉิงชอบคุณหลีใช่ไหม
You should ask the guy himself.
ปัญหานี้คุณควรไปถามเจ้าตัวเองนะ
You know them the best.
คุณรู้จักพวกเขาดีที่สุด
You can answer me from an objective point of view.
ถามคุณเป็นกลางกว่า
The only thing I can tell you confidently
สิ่งที่ผมยืนยันกับคุณได้
is that they used to date each other.
มีแค่พวกเขาเคยคบกัน
Did Miss Li come back
งั้นที่คุณหลีกลับมา
because she wanted to get back together with Jiang Yicheng?
อยากที่จะกลับคืนดีกับเจียงอี้เฉิงเหรอ
You are now married to Yicheng.
ตอนนี้คุณกับอี้เฉิงก็แต่งงานกันแล้ว
Nothing will happen between them.
ระหว่างพวกเขาไม่มีอะไรหรอก
If we end our marriage,
ถ้าเกิดการแต่งงานของเราจบลงล่ะ
will they get back together?
พวกเขาก็จะคบกันได้ใช่ไหม
How can you end a marriage so easily?
การแต่งงานจะจบลงง่าย ๆ แบบนั้นได้ไง
It's difficult to end a real marriage,
ของจริงคงไม่ได้
but not a fake one.
แต่ของปลอมได้
What are you talking about?
คุณว่าอะไรนะ
Jiang Yicheng and I have a contract-based marriage.
ฉันกับเจียงอี้เฉิงแต่งงานกันตามสัญญา
This is why he said
ที่แท้ที่ก่อนหน้านี้อี้เฉิงบอกว่าซับซ้อน
that it's complicated.
ก็หมายความแบบนี้
Yicheng's family wanted him to get married.
บ้านอี้เฉิงเร่งให้ไปดูตัว
I can understand why he got married.
แรงกระตุ้นที่เขาแต่งงานผมเข้าใจได้
But why did you agree to that?
แต่ว่าคุณทำไมทำแบบนี้
I got to know Jiang Yicheng a long time ago
ฉันรู้จักเจียงอี้เฉิงมานานแล้ว
through a game named "Dream Maker".
ในเกม"นักสร้างฝัน" นั้น
It has been...
ปีนี้
five years since I fell for him.
เป็นปีที่ห้าที่ฉันชอบเขา
You joined the company because of Yicheng.
ดังนั้นคุณมาที่บริษัทเพราะอี้เฉิง
I couldn't understand
ก่อนหน้านี้ผมก็แปลกใจมาตลอด
why did you agree to that arrangement.
ว่าทำไมคุณรับปากแต่งงาน
I didn't expect this to be the reason.
คิดไม่ถึงว่าจะเป็นเหตุผลนี้
I read a quote
ก่อนหน้านี้ฉัน
from Shakespeare before.
เคยเห็นประโยคหนึ่งของเชกสเปียร์
When we can't afford happiness,
ตอนที่พวกเราซื้อความสุขไม่ได้
we should never walk too close to the window.
ก็อย่าอยู่ใกล้ตู้โชว์เกินไป
I thought
ฉันก็เหมือนกับ
my happiness was within reach,
คนที่คิดไปเองว่าความสุขอยู่ไม่ไกล
but I was actually standing outside the window the whole time.
แต่สุดท้ายเป็นแค่คนที่ยืนอยู่หน้าตู้โชว์
Lu Li.
ลู่หลี
We earn what we fight for.
มีหลายเรื่องที่ได้มาเพราะความพยายามนะ
I earned myself a year.
ฉันพยายามชิงเวลามาให้ตัวเองหนึ่งปี
At least, for the coming year,
ฉันคิดว่าอย่างน้อยในหนึ่งปีนี้
he's mine.
เขาก็เป็นของฉัน
But plans always fall behind changes.
แต่ว่าแผนการก็มักจะ ห้ามเรื่องไม่คาดฝันไม่ได้
You have to believe in Yicheng.
คุณจะต้องมั่นใจในตัวอี้เฉิงนะ
If he can't give you the affection you want,
ต่อให้ตอนนี้เขาให้ความรัก ที่คุณต้องการไม่ได้
you have to believe in him.
คุณก็ต้องเชื่อใจเขา
What are you doing?
พวกนายทำอะไรกัน
I'm comforting her as a friend.
เพื่อนปลอบใจกัน
Why do you need comfort?
ทำไมคุณต้องการให้ปลอบใจ
Her husband brought her along to meet his ex-girlfriend.
ถูกสามีพามานัดของแฟนเก่า
Anyone will get upset too.
คนปกติก็มีอารมณ์ทั้งนั้น
Husband?
สามีอะไร
Senior.
รุ่นพี่
What do you mean?
หมายความว่าไง
Isn't she Yicheng's girlfriend?
ลู่หลีไม่ใช่แฟนของอี้เฉิงเหรอ
I've never said that she's my girlfriend.
ผมไม่เคยบอกว่าเขาเป็นแฟนผม
Let me introduce her again.
ขอแนะนำใหม่อีกที
She's my wife.
เขาเป็นภรรยาของผม
Lu Li.
ลู่หลี
We shall go.
พวกเราไปละ
Li Man.
หลีม่าน
Senior.
รุ่นพี่
I've got to go.
ฉันกลับก่อนนะ
Have you ever regretted what you did?
คุณเคยเสียใจไหม
When I was abroad,
ฉันรู้สึกเสียใจในทุกวันที่ฉัน
I lived every day in regret
อยู่ต่างประเทศ
and talking myself out of the regret.
แล้วก็ผ่านด้วยการบอกว่าตัวเองไม่เสียใจ
The only thing
ชีวิตนี้ของผม
I regret
เรื่องเสียใจอย่างเดียวที่เคยทำ
is letting you join the company.
ก็คือเสียใจที่ให้คุณเข้ามาบริษัท
If it wasn't for you,
ถ้าไม่มีคุณ
Yicheng might have already become
บางทีตอนนี้อี้เฉิงคง
the top in the gaming industry.
อยู่ระดับท็อปของวงการเกมแล้ว
If I had a choice,
ถ้าตอนนั้นมีทางเลือก
I wouldn't have done what I did.
ฉันไม่มีทางเดินทางนี้แน่
I don't want to know the reason behind your doing.
ผมไม่อยากถามว่าทำไม สามปีก่อนคุณถึงทำแบบนี้
What has happened, has happened.
เพราะเรื่องที่ผ่านไปแล้ว คงแก้ไขอะไรไม่ได้
What matters now is the present and the future.
ที่สำคัญอยู่ที่ตอนนี้และอนาคต
You saw it yourself.
คุณก็เห็นแล้ว
Yicheng has started all over again.
ตอนนี้อี้เฉิงเริ่มต้นใหม่แล้ว
I hope
ผมหวังว่า
you can do the same too.
คุณ...ก็สามารถ
You have said so much,
รุ่นพี่ พี่พูดขนาดนี้
and all you want is for me to give up.
เพื่อให้ฉันยอมแพ้ใช่ไหม
Yes.
ใช่
I came back for Yicheng.
ครั้งนี้ฉันกลับมาเพราะอี้เฉิง
But I don't like interfering in others' marriages.
แต่ว่าฉันไม่ได้ชอบจะแทรกแซงชีวิตคู่ใคร
I only found out about this.
ฉันก็เพิ่งรู้เมื่อกี้
I need some time to process this.
ฉันแค่ต้องการเวลาทำใจ
I've got to go.
ไปก่อนละ
Wait a minute.
รอเดี๋ยว
I didn't tell you about the dinner beforehand
เรื่องอาหารค่ำที่ไม่ได้บอกคุณก่อน
because...
ก็เพราะว่า...
Is she the female programmer who ditched you?
เขาก็คือโปรแกรมเมอร์หญิง ที่ทิ้งคุณคนนั้นเหรอ
Although we are legally married,
คุณอย่าคิดนะว่าเราจดทะเบียนกันแล้ว
you can't speculate about my past.
ก็จะเที่ยวมาคาดเดาเรื่องของผมได้
I didn't speculate.
ฉันไม่ได้เที่ยวคาดเดา
I only have to apply some logic.
นี่คือตรรกะพื้นฐาน
You took care of me in front of Miss Li.
ต่อหน้าคุณหลีคุณทำเป็นใส่ใจดูแลฉัน
Weren't you trying to use me as an excuse?
ไม่ใช่ว่าเอาฉันมาบังหน้าเหรอ
Then, what about you and Chen Yiming?
แล้วคุณกับเฉินอี้หมิงล่ะ
He was comforting me.
เขากำลังปลอบใจฉัน
Why did he have to comfort you?
ปลอบใจอะไรคุณ
It was about work.
เรื่องงาน
If it was about work, why did he have to hug you?
เรื่องงานจะต้องโอบกันด้วยเหรอ
If there is anything more serious,
งั้นเรื่องที่ร้ายแรงกว่านั้น
will you cheat on me?
หัวผมนี่จะไม่เรืองแสงสีเขียวเลยเหรอ [*หมายความว่าถูกสวมเขา]
Li Man and you...
คุณกับหลีม่าน...
There's nothing between us.
ผมกับเขาไม่มีอะไรทั้งนั้น
You haven't answered me.
คุณยังไม่ตอบคำถามผมเลย
I don't want to answer all these ridiculous questions.
ฉันไม่อยากตอบคำถามที่ไร้เหตุผลของคุณ
Let me go.
ปล่อย
(Lu Li.)
(ลู่หลี)
(Aren't you allergic to seafood?)
(นี่คุณแพ้อาหารทะเลเหรอ)
(Jiuzhou Pharmacy)
(ร้านขายยาจิ่วโจว)
(Hi.)
สวัสดีครับ
(Do you have any medicine for seafood allergies?)
มียาแก้แพ้อาหารทะเลไหมครับ
(Are you the patient?)
ตัวคุณแพ้เองหรือเปล่าคะ
No.
ไม่ใช่ครับ
It's for my wife.
ภรรยาผมครับ
She took a bite of the shrimp and has got rashes all over her neck.
เขากินกุ้งไปคำเดียวคอก็ขึ้นตุ่มแดง
This is for topical application.
ยาทาภายนอก
Don't scratch it to avoid inflammation.
อย่าเกานะคะจะได้ไม่อักเสบ
Is there anything else I should pay attention to?
มีอะไรที่ต้องระวังอีกไหมครับ
Before she recovers,
ช่วงนี้
she should avoid spicy food.
ก็พยายามเลี่ยงของแสลงก่อน
If it gets worse, it's advised to seek medical help.
ถ้าอาการหนักแนะนำ ให้ไปตรวจที่โรงพยาบาล
Thank you.
ขอบคุณครับ
What a fool.
ยัยบ๊อง
You shouldn't eat the seafood if you can't.
กินอาหารทะเลไม่ได้ยังอวดเก่งอีก
That...
คือว่า
I bought you breakfast.
ผมซื้ออาหารเช้ามา
The doctor advised you to eat healthy and light food.
หมอบอกว่าคุณต้องกินอาหารอ่อน ๆ
Didn't she see the ointment I bought for her?
เขาไม่เห็นว่าฉันซื้อยามาให้เหรอ
Where are you going?
คุณจะไปไหน
Are you going to walk?
ไม่นั่งรถเหรอ
She's giving me the cold shoulder.
ถึงกับเย็นชาใส่ฉัน
Do as you please.
ไม่นั่งก็ช่าง
I can't be bothered to drive you around.
ใครสนใจอยากพาคุณไป
I'm already giving in.
นี่ฉันให้ทางลงเขาแล้ว
Yet, she didn't appreciate it.
เขาไม่ลง
I won't apologize
ให้ฉันขอโทษอีกเหรอ
again.
ไม่มีทาง
Koala Lu is usually quite tractable.
ปกติแล้วโคอาลาลู่ก็เชื่อฟังดี
Why is she so angry this time?
ทำไมครั้งนี้โกรธขนาดนี้
I personally think that Koala is a docile animal.
ส่วนตัวคิดว่าโคอาลานิสัยเชื่อง
It's unlikely that it will get angry.
โอกาสโมโหน้อยมาก
It's really unlikely that she will get angry.
โอกาสโมโหน้อยมากจริง
But once she's angry,
แต่พอโมโหขึ้นมาที
she's really fierce.
ก็อารมณ์ร้อนมากเลยเหอะ
If you want the correct answer,
ถ้าคุณอยากจะรู้คำตอบที่ถูกต้องละก็
you can approach Koala itself.
แนะนำให้คุณไปถามโคอาลา
What a lousy answer.
คำตอบบ้าอะไรเนี่ย
(Koala got angry because it was drenched)
(โคอาลาก็โกรธเป็น ความซวยถูกน้ำสาดใส่)
(The koala was drenched by accident.) The resemblance is uncanny.
เหมือนกันเด๊ะเลย
(Sorry)
(ขอโทษ)
I'm the boss.
ฉันเป็นเจ้านายนะ
She is my staff.
เขาเป็นพนักงาน
She should be the one
จะขอโทษ
apologizing to me.
ยังไงก็ควรให้เขาขอโทษฉัน
No.
ไม่ได้
(Come to the office)
(มาที่ออฟฟิศ)
(We're all afraid of losing the person we love.)
(มีความรู้สึกอย่างหนึ่ง เรียกว่าวิตกกังวลว่าจะได้หรือเสีย)
(When we fall for someone,)
(เพราะว่าชอบคนอื่นคนเราก็)
(we often become humble.)
(มักจะรู้สึกต่ำต้อย)
(However, we forget that if we keep chasing after the light,)
(แต่ลืมไปว่าถ้าเอาแต่วิ่งไล่ตามแสง)
(the light will never see us.)
(แสงก็ไม่มีวันเห็นคุณที่อยู่ด้านหลัง)
♪Tall and big, you have a childish voice♪
♪คุณตัวสูง ๆ มีน้ำเสียงเป็นเด็กน้อย♪
♪Naive♪
♪ใสซื่อมาก♪
♪Petty♪
♪ใจแคบมาก♪
♪Small and little, I feel a little stressed around you♪
♪ฉันตัวเล็ก ๆ อยู่ข้างคุณกดดันนิดหน่อย♪
♪Afraid to go near♪
♪ไม่ค่อยกล้าเข้าใกล้♪
♪I hope to see you every morning♪
♪หวังจะได้เจอคุณในทุก ๆ เช้า♪
♪So that my day can be meaningful♪
♪แบบนี้หนึ่งวันที่ผ่านไปจึงจะมีความหมาย♪
♪Waiting to hear your voice every night♪
♪ทุกคืนเฝ้ารอเสียงรบกวนของคุณ♪
♪To break the silence of the night♪
♪ทำลายความเงียบงันในค่ำคืนนี้♪
♪Every time the phone rings, I wish it were you♪
♪เสียงโทรศัพท์ดังขึ้นในใจ ภาวนาให้เป็นคุณ♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪แค่เสียงคุณดังขึ้น♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪ใบหน้าก็มีรอยยิ้มสดใส♪
♪Your words are always a little childish♪
♪คำพูดของคุณมักดูเป็นเด็กน้อย♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪เลยแกล้งคุณประจำ♪
♪Sorry♪
♪ขอโทษที♪
♪Sometimes you're a little stubborn♪
♪บางครั้งคุณก็เอาแต่ใจไปบ้าง♪
♪A bad temper♪
♪นิสัยไม่ดี♪
♪With a touch of jealousy♪
♪ขี้หึงบ้าง ♪
♪So I'll just have to coax you and let you have your way♪
♪ดังนั้นฉันเลยทำได้แค่ยอมคุณ ปลอบคุณ♪
♪Hurry, hurry, go away rain♪
♪เร็วสิ ฝนผ่านไปแล้วท้องฟ้าสดใส♪
♪I hope to see you every morning♪
♪หวังจะได้เจอคุณในทุก ๆ เช้า♪
♪So that my day can be meaningful♪
♪แบบนี้หนึ่งวันที่ผ่านไปจึงจะมีความหมาย♪
♪Waiting to hear your voice every night♪
♪ทุกคืนเฝ้ารอเสียงรบกวนของคุณ♪
♪To break the silence of the night♪
♪ทำลายความเงียบงันในค่ำคืนนี้♪
♪This song is for you, the one I love the most♪
♪เพลงนี้มอบให้แด่คุณสุดที่รัก♪
♪We'll walk down the path of the future together♪
♪เส้นทางต่อไปข้างหน้า พวกเราเดินไปด้วยกัน♪
♪Every time the phone rings, I wish it were you♪
♪เสียงโทรศัพท์ดังขึ้นในใจ ภาวนาให้เป็นคุณ♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪แค่เสียงคุณดังขึ้น♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪ใบหน้าก็มีรอยยิ้มสดใส♪
♪Your words are always a little childish♪
♪คำพูดของคุณมักดูเป็นเด็กน้อย♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪เลยแกล้งคุณประจำ♪
♪Sorry♪
♪ขอโทษที♪
♪Never mind♪
♪ไม่เป็นไร♪
♪I love you♪
♪ฉันรักคุณ♪